doxtop.com 2012-10-22

# Privacy | doXtop

English

Data Protection Declaration (privacy policy)

doXtop requires users who are authors (see "General terms and conditions of use - Foreword") to register. Persons who are only readers and access published / released data, are not registered. Within the scope of registration and admission to the platform, personal data are collected. With the application to admission to the platform and subsequent registration, the User expressly consents to the collection and pertinent use of such data. In the process, doXtop devotes its best efforts to protecting such data. In what follows we explain what data and information are collected, what is done with this data, and what rights the provider of the data has: 

1\. Personal data

Collected are personal data relating to the identity of the User. These are, for example, the true and correct name, e-mail address, telephone number of the User. 

Collection and storage of such information: 

This information is collected on first application and registration, and checked each time the User logs in. The User can make contributions to the doXtop platform only with a valid log-in. doXtop stores these data in a specially protected server.

2. The information is not passed on to third parties

doXtop uses the personal data exclusively to identify the User and to manage the platform. The information is passed on to third parties only if the User has declared his express consent thereto. 

Furthermore, the User can himself determine whether and which of his personal data may be publicly displayed. 

3. Security measures

doXtop takes seriously the protection of users' personal data from unauthorized access, improper use, falsification and accidental loss. Nevertheless, doXtop cannot guarantee protection of the User's personal data. Due to the nature of the internet, it is impossible to rule out altogether the possibility of other users appropriating the personal data which the User has placed on doXtop's internet page, and result in undesirable communications by other users. To the extent that User data are made public by the User himself, they are also available to the public. 

4. User's access to transmitted data

doXtop will keep a record of the User's consent to the collection and use of the data. The User can call up the text of his consent at any time. Furthermore, the User can revoke his consent at any time and delete the communicated data himself at any time. 

5. Cookies

Cookies are small text files which are used by thousands of websites in order to identify regular visitors. With the help of such cookies doXtop can analyse how users make use of doXtop websites. doXtop can then tailor the contents of its sites exactly to the needs of users. Over and above this, doXtop has the possibility of measuring how effective advertising is and to regulate its appearance accordingly so that it can be placed, for example, to suit the themes that are of interest to users. 

If the User does not wish to take make use of the advantages offered by cookies, the User may activate or deactivate them in his browser with the help of a simple procedure. 

6. Amendment of the Data Protection Declaration 

Amendments to the Data Protection Declaration may become necessary from time to time. doXtop reserves the right to amend the text of the Data Protection Declaration at any time in compliance with data protection laws. Every amendment will be published as a new version on the doXtop internet page. The User is responsible for keeping himself informed of any changes made to the Data Protection Declaration. Through his continued use of the doX doXtop top platform, the User shall be deemed to have given his consent to any such amendments.

7. Supplementary information

If you as a potential or actual User have any questions you wish to ask relating to data protection, you can do so by sending an e-mail to the following address:  

Datenschutzerklärung (privacy policy)

doXtop verlangt von Nutzern, die Autoren sind (vergleiche allgemeine Nutzungsbedingungen – Vorwort …) eine Registrierung. Wer nur Leser ist und auf publizierte/freigegebene Daten zugreift, wird nicht registriert. Im Rahmen der Registrierung und Zulassung zur Plattform werden personenbezogene Daten erhoben. Mit dem Antrag auf Zulassung zur Plattform und der entsprechenden Registrierung willigt der Nutzer in die Erhebung und zweckbestimmte Verwendung dieser Daten ausdrücklich ein. Dabei ist doXtop um bestmögliche Wahrung des Datenschutzes bemüht. Nachstehend erklären wir, welche Daten/Informationen erhoben werden, was mit diesen Daten unternommen wird und welche Rechte dem Inhaber der Daten zustehen: 

1. Personenbezogene Informationen

Erhoben werden persönliche Informationen zur Identität des Nutzers. Dies sind z. B. der richtige, wirkliche Name, E-Mail-Adresse, Telefonnummer. 

Sammlung und Speicherung der Informationen

Die Informationen werden bei der ersten Anmeldung und Registrierung erfasst und bei jedem Login des Nutzers geprüft. Das Einstellen von Beiträgen durch den Nutzer auf der Plattform von doXtop ist nur mit gültigem Login möglich. Die Angaben werden bei doXtop auf einem besonders geschützten Server gespeichert.

2. Keine Weitergabe von Informationen 

doXtop verwendet die personenbezogenen Informationen ausschließlich für die Identifizierung des Nutzers und die Verwaltung der Plattform. An Dritte werden die Informationen allenfalls dann weitergegeben, wenn der Nutzer sein ausdrückliches Einverständnis dazu erklärt hat. 

Der Nutzer kann darüber hinaus selber festlegen, ob und welche seiner Daten öffentlich angezeigt werden. 

3. Sicherheitsmaßnahmen

doXtop nimmt den Schutz der persönlichen Daten der Nutzer vor unautorisiertem Zugriff, unangemessenem Gebrauch, Verfälschung sowie ungewolltem Verlust ernst. Trotzdem kann doXtop den Schutz der persönlichen Informationen des Nutzers nicht garantieren; bedingt durch die Natur des Internets kann nicht mit letzter Konsequenz ausgeschlossen werden, dass die persönlichen Daten, die der Nutzer auf der Internetseite von doXtop gemacht hat, von anderen Nutzern aufgenommen werden können und zu unerwünschten Nachrichten von anderen Internetnutzern führen können. Soweit die Nutzerdaten vom Nutzer selber öffentlich gemacht werden, sind sie auch öffentlich verfügbar. 

4. Zugriff des Nutzers auf die übermittelten Daten

Die Einwilligung des Nutzers zur Erhebung und Verwendung der Daten wird von doXtop protokolliert. Der Nutzer kann den Inhalt der Einwilligung jederzeit abrufen. Ferner kann der Nutzer jederzeit die Einwilligung widerrufen und die mitgeteilten Daten selber wieder löschen. 

5. Cookies

Cookies sind kleine Textdateien, die von tausenden Websites verwendet werden, um regelmäßige Besucher zu identifizieren. Mit Hilfe solcher Cookies kann doXtop analysieren, wie Nutzer die Websites von doXtop benutzen. doXtop kann dann Inhalte seiner Sites genau auf die Bedürfnisse der Benutzer abstimmen. Darüber hinaus hat doXtop die Möglichkeit, die Effektivität von Anzeigen zu messen und ihre Schaltung entsprechend zu steuern, sodass ihre Platzierung zum Beispiel abhängig von den thematischen Interessen der Nutzer erfolgt. 

Wenn der Nutzer die Vorteile der Cookies nicht nutzen will, kann der Nutzer diese mit Hilfe eines einfachen Verfahrens in seinem Browser aktivieren oder deaktivieren. 

6. Änderung der Datenschutzerklärung

Von Zeit zu Zeit können Änderungen der Datenschutzerklärung notwendig werden. doXtop behält sich das Recht vor, den Inhalt der Datenschutzerklärung jederzeit unter Beachtung der datenschutzrechtlichen Vorgaben zu ändern. Jede etwaige Änderung wird als eine neue Version auf der Internetseite von doXtop veröffentlicht. Der Nutzer ist selbst dafür verantwortlich, sich über etwaige Änderungen der Datenschutzerklärung zu informieren. Durch die weitergehende Nutzung der doXtop Plattform erklärt der Nutzer sein Einverständnis mit den Änderungen. 

7\. Ergänzende Informationen

Sofern Sie als potentieller oder tatsächlicher Nutzer noch ergänzende Fragen zum Datenschutz haben, können Sie dies uns per E-Mail an folgende Adresse mitteilen:  

Stand 21.08.2007
